<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Francisco Carreño]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Francisco Carreño]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/fcarreno/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 19:18:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/fcarreno/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skepticism: A Double Edge Sword]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Skepticism: A Double Edge Sword</h1><p>Be skeptical, but don't be automatic in your rejection. You might enter an absurd state of denial. Be skeptical, but be willing to test your
own skepticism without looking for self-confirmation, nor praising for your
ego. Be skeptical, but be humble. Embrace the
possibility of being wrong as an opportunity to increase your knowledge,
appreciate life, and grow your mind and soul. Be skeptical, but be constructive. The fact
that you might not believe something does not entitle you to disrespect those
who believe different. You would be amazed if you practiced more empathy than
trying to prove your point. Be skeptical, but don't use your skepticism
as a tool to justify your laziness to learn, or as way to avoid the work that
is required to test your point. If you are not willing to find out whether you
are right or whether you might have to learn something, don’t even bother to
manifest your skepticism. It will be a total waste of time. Be skeptical, but be self-aware, since your
lack of capability or understanding does not equal that the object, product,
achievement or service you are skeptical about is not real. It might be totally
real despite your comprehension. Using skepticism as a way to hide
ignorance makes the person who tries to do it look like an idiot. Be skeptical, but remain
curious. Skepticism is an amazing tool with the power of transforming
people’s lives and the whole world. However, being skeptical about something
without curiosity is pointless. It is incomplete. Be thorough and make sure
that when you show your skepticism, you also present your curiosity in order to
advance knowledge. If you want to summarize the whole idea in one punch line: Be skeptical, but don't be an idiot</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/fcarreno/skepticism-a-double-edge-sword/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">452a1ec4-5116-42da-8341-73ae65246a26</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 19:18:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>